You look nice
if you wear it like this.
And what can I do for you two?
It's payday.
Give us the envelope.
Your boss has been missing
for months.
Kabukicho belongs
to Chihara-kai.
End of story. So get lost.
Give us the envelope. Or we come back
tonight and do that to all your hosts.
- Get them some money.
- Yes ma'am.
You feel like a big boy now,
don't you?
Enjoy it while it lasts.
Today we have journalist from
Meicho Shimbun as our guest.
Thank you for being here.
Your feature article about
the Bosozoku motorcycle gangs
has drawn much interest.
How do you feel about
all the attention?
It's not about me.
I've spent a lot of time
with these young people.
They're a part of society
we don't hear from.
And now you've written
a follow-up on those reasons.
Do you feel your status as an outsider
gives you a unique perspective?
I'd say it gives...
I came off like an asshole.
No. You sounded thoughtful.
And looked very, very handsome.
- Your friends are very cute.
- I know. I tell them all the time.
That's just my friend. Samantha.
- St. Louis?
- Yeah.
It's to go home
for my dad's 60th birthday.
And the Meicho will let their star
reporter have time off?
Do you not want to go?
No, it's just kind of complicated
with my family.
Plus, I'd rather stay here
with you.
- Spend the day with me.
- You know I can't.
Then let's go out tonight.
Just once.
We do go out.
Our rendezvous spot?
That's not going out.
Aren't you tired of sneaking over here,
and never leaving this room?
Jake.
You know it's too dangerous.
I'm tired of hiding.
I am too. But we have to be patient.
And careful.
Because I'm really good
at being patient and careful.
Hiroshi Shibuya.
Just arrested for stabbing a man
while trying to collect a debt.
- Yakuza foot soldier.
- Mr. Shibuya, well done. And?
He was doing so on behalf
of his organization.
Perfect. And his affiliation?
The Hishinuma-kai.
Small. Low on funds, and men.
The test case
we've been seeking.
How many men do you think
we'll need?
Excuse me.
I've been summoned upstairs
by Yabuki-san.
- Is there anything else you need?
- No.
Someone is outside if that
should change.
I'll return later
with the children.
Hagino.
Yes, ma'am?
You've been working hard
these last months.
Thank you.
You look pale.
Get some sun and take vitamins.
Please...
Take care of yourself.
- Yes?
- How is Mrs. Tozawa?
Same routine, no changes.
You summoned us?
You thought I wouldn't find out?
You will return the money to Club
Miralina. And stay out of Kabukicho.
How can we stand by while Chihara-kai
keeps taking what's ours?
Tozawa-kumicho would never stand
for this.
He needs a lesson.
You do it.
Now.
Harder.
Get them out of here.
What?
The others also don't
understand.
Chihara-kai is slowly taking
everything of ours.
And we do nothing.
Our men are growing restless
and angry.
They don't need to understand.
They need to do
what I tell them.
You can go.
Yes.
Excuse me.
You're an asshole.
Why don't you
let me cook for you?
Come to my house.
I'll make you a meal.
- You wanna make me a meal?
- Yes, I do.
How nice of you, Ohno-san.
- Please call me Masa.
- Gladly.
So, what do you say?
- I'm flattered.
- Which usually means no.
- It's just that I have rules.
- Samantha.
I feel we've made a real connection
these last weeks.
I'd like to see where it goes.
If you're willing.
Let me think about it.
Sure.
What are you doing?
You got our pretty girl all wet.
If you're gonna
throw something, throw it right.
I'll just be a minute. Sure.
Good evening, Ohno-san.
May I join you for a moment?
I would be delighted.
Are you gonna do
something about this?
There's nothing I can do.
Welcome!
Is everyone enjoying themselves?
Drinks are watery. Work on that.
I would be grateful if you
and your colleagues
could enjoy your night
with less exuberance.
If pretty boy comes over here and tells us
to keep it down, we will.
Until then, get out of my face.
I don't appreciate being
spoken to like that.
I'm not gonna ask you
nicely again.
Excuse me.
From that gentleman over there.
Now that's more like it.
We'll have this, then we'll go.
Excuse me.
Thanks for driving me
home again.
I don't mind.
I'm always starving after work.
- Want to go somewhere?
- I have to get home.
But I have leftovers I can heat up.
Would you like some?
Yes.
I need to pay the babysitter. Do you mind
staying here for a moment?
Take your time.
Who are you?
Sato.
- Where's mama?
- With your sitter.
Why are you up?
You woke me.
I see.
Sorry.
- You should go back to bed.
- I will.
If you read to me.
Let's go.
"You're baking a cake, aren't you?
It smells so yummy."
"All the animals in the woods
wiggling their noses."
- Mama.
- I'm home.
- Welcome back.
- He woke up and I wanted me to...
Thank you.
Time to say goodnight.
Goodnight, night owl.
Goodnight.
- Do you have to go?
- No.
- I'm still hungry.
- I'll be right out.
Time to sleep, Dai-chan.
Night owl.
Put your arms in.
Go to sleep.
That was delicious.
You just like it
because of the company.
That might be true.
You're not what I expected.
What did you expect?
Another tattooed guy.
Like all the others.
You're not what I expected either.
What did you expect?
That you'd be boring.
I'm not boring.
See you soon.
Bye.
Last night was the third time this month
that he's been in my club.
He's chasing my clients away.
Who the fuck is he?
Hayama.
He's the wakagashira of Chihara-kai.
Ishida's number two.
Sato's supposed to look after my club.
Last night, he just sat there.
He wouldn't lift a finger
to help me.
Yeah, there's not much he can do,
'cause Hayama outranks him.
Will you talk to him for me?
See if he can do something.
To Sato?
The last time I saw Sato, I got kicked out
of Onyx for trying to fight him.
So, we stay clear of each other.
Why don't you talk to him?
I thought
you guys were, like...
Not anymore.
Business and pleasure,
not a great mix.
- Yeah. I hear that.
- Are you seeing someone?
Yeah.
For a while now.
It's really good.
I mean, it's complicated. But it's good.
- Look at you, all grown up.
- Well, let's not go that far.
I can't have this guy in my club.
Go to Sato as a friend.
And ask for his help.
"I appreciate having my eyes opened
to the state of juvenile delinquency."
"Moreover, I was surprised that
it was written by a foreign reporter."
Yeah!
Two articles about motorcycle thieves,
and now, you're a hero.
Don't do that. Cynicism is lazy.
I agree. It's our mission
to try and change things.
Yes, try and change things.
But why do Americans think
it's your job to fix the entire world?
Well, someone's gotta do it.
I have to get back to work.
But take these.
Invitations to an official function
at the U.S. Ambassador's residence.
Tomorrow night.
You're all going.
To cultivate sources.
Have a good night.
It's nice to see the boss let
her hair down.
I don't think she has much time
for fun.
How did he do in his last game?
He hit a home run.
He was so proud.
I'm sure you were too.
Hey.
How many members of the Meicho's A/V
department have you talked with?
All of them.
Off the record.
They all said the same thing.
None of them could have started
that fire.
And you believe them?
So someone at the Meicho
was willing
to burn down the building
to destroy that evidence.
We don't know that.
Emi. Don't let your loyalty keep
you from seeing that place clearly.
You are too talented for that.
Damn it.
- I have to go.
- He'll be fine. Just call him.
He doesn't answer the phone.
I'll come with you.
Enough of us hiding.
For months now.
Because your brother's too
fragile to know about me?
- He's not fragile, he's sick.
- Emi.
He doesn't have a stomachache.
Your brother is mentally ill.
This can't go on.
Things have to change.
He's my brother.
I have to go.
Next up is
"Book IV No1 In A Flat Major"
by Felix Mendelssohn.
I thought we were
meeting here next week.
This couldn't wait.
- Is this a plane ticket to Missouri?
- No, it's better.
It's an invitation
to a U.S. Embassy party.
Tomorrow night.
You're gonna be my plus-one.
We invent a name for you,
and get you on the list.
- Jake. It's still such a risk.
- It's just one night.
You and me.
On a real date.
It's perfect.
What's this?
Oh, you're back.
Remember you said you were
craving Dwaeji-gukbap?
I saw we had most
of the ingredients.
- Smells good, yeah?
- Very good.
Right? Will you watch the soup
while I cut more cabbage?
Sure.
A way out, but there was none
Now, I will punish myself
Everybody
Rock your body
Rock your body right
Backstreet's back, all right
- I love this song!
- Really? You love it?
You know this group?
Hey. You know these guys?
Get outta here.
You're next.
I'm okay.
Come on, we all have to do it.
I'm going next.
Shut up! I'm singing!
- You sound like a cat in heat.
- Hey! Let him finish!
You meet Hayama yet?
Who's Hayama?
Your brother doesn't
tell you shit, does he?
What did I tell you?
No business tonight. Just fun.
You're not one of us.
Are you?
Hey.
I just left you a message
about meeting up.
I was already on my way here.
I need to talk to you, too.
Okay.
We have a problem.
You mean about Hayama?
Will you talk to Ishida?
Make him understand
Hayama's bad for business.
The Oyabun will keep him
out of the club.
After you do something for him.
The architect.
- Ohno-san? What about him?
- He works for the city.
Chief designer
of a new shopping center.
To be built
on a railway station.
The Oyabun wants to know
which station before it's public.
To buy all the surrounding land.
Before the announcement
makes it prime real estate.
I'm not spying
on a customer for you.
The success of my place
depends on discretion.
For Oyabun,
knowing which railway station
is more valuable than the club.
And the club belongs to him.
- So, now you're threatening me?
- I told you not to fire Claudine.
- She was fucking stealing from me.
- She was working for us.
She was sitting
with the architect every night.
Getting information.
But now, all he wants is you.
So, you must finish the job.
And if I say no?
Please, trust me.
Do not say no.
I'm sorry.
I'll need your answer tomorrow.
This is the layout of the Hishinuma-kai
headquarters.
We enter here.
We make sure this door
is blocked.
Many of you have been on yakuza
raids with me before.
This one will be different.
Deputy Superintendent Nagata
will explain.
To begin with,
we neglected to make an
appointment for today's visit.
Our goal is to charge them with
obstructing police duty.
To do so, they have to physically put
a hand on one of us.
I will ensure that happens.
What?
You have something to say?
I said... It's about time, sir.
- Yes.
- Alright!
- Shall we?
- Yes, sir!
- Move.
On behalf of Oyabun Ishida,
we are honored that Hishinuma-san
accepts his offer.
Spare me the speech, Kobayashi.
If my organization
were stronger,
we would not be joining yours.
I understand.
But... these are difficult times
for all of us.
And our terms
are more than fair.
Fine, let's get this over with.
Police! Open up!
Did they make an appointment?
What do they want?
Is Hiroshi Shibuya here?
He hasn't been around in weeks.
But he is an associate?
- Yeah.
- Don't answer that.
Your colleague has been arrested
on charges of stabbing a man.
In the performance of his duties
as a member of the Hishinuma-kai.
I regret that Hishinuma-kai
did not receive notice of your visit.
- If one of our associates...
- We're not here to make deals!
Mr. Shibuya's criminal liability
extends to his employer.
Mr. Hishinuma.
You're under arrest.
The rest of you will be taken in
for questioning on suspicion of
being accessories to extortion.
What the hell are you
talking about?
Wait, lady.
You afraid of me?
Why don't you run home to mama?
What'd you say?
You're under arrest for
Obstruction of Police Duty.
Now!
He didn't do anything!
Protect the Oyabun!
Don't touch me!
We're not in this gumi!
Go!
Fuck off!
Don't.
You don't want to be
a cop killer.
How many yakuza organizations
are there in this city? Detective?
Twenty-five.
Now there's twenty-four.
Next week, twenty-three.
This war against the Yakuza
is just beginning.
Did you really charge them with
Obstruction of Police Duty?
Yes, we did.
But that's only used for
political protestors.
Until now.
Old law, new twist.
And we're just getting started.
To Deputy Superintendent Nagata!
- Hello?
- How are you, little bean?
I'm drawing a car.
Your red one.
We will have to make space
to hang it.
Can you put Mommy on the phone?
She told me to tell you she's too tired
for the phone tonight.
Then...
- Please tell her I called.
- Bye-bye.
In daylights, in sunsets
In midnights
In cups of coffee
In inches, in miles
In laughter, in strife
How about love
Do you know this music?
It is an American folk song.
From their country's founding.
Seasons of love
Here we go.
Thank you
to the cast members of Rent.
So, please, say hi to them
as you enjoy something to eat.
- I'm going to try out the cream puffs.
- I'll see you later.
You're eating cream puffs now?
It's okay, but...
Who's that girl with Jake?
- I don't know. Why?
- I've seen her somewhere before.
I'm going inside.
Lynn is in the FBI, so she only deals
with federal crimes.
Well, at least American law
acknowledges the problem.
Women in the U.S. can take out
restraining orders against their stalkers.
Yes, that's true, but we could be
a lot more effective with prevention.
If you'd like, I can get you
the latest American statistics.
- I would. Can we talk on Monday?
- Absolutely.
Did you get some tasty fish
that comes in balloons?
Yes.
I had the shrimp puffs.
They were delicious.
Jason Aoki, U.S. Embassy.
Jun Shinohara, Meicho Shimbun.
A journalist?
I was wrong.
My colleagues and I play a game
where we try to guess
what people do
before we meet them.
- What were the guesses?
- One did guess journalist.
One bet retired baseball player.
I just lost money
betting you were a model.
You should meet
another of our reporters.
Jake Adelstein,
this is Lynn Oberfeld.
Legal Attaché at the Embassy.
I've really enjoyed
reading your work.
When Hal Lieberman first said
there was an American
working on the Meicho,
I thought he was kidding.
We are slowly civilizing him.
This is Jason Aoki,
from my office.
- Nice to meet you.
- And you. This is my friend, Mari.
Journalist also?
No, I'm a choreographer.
Modern dance.
Oh, forgive me, I see a colleague
from the Korean Embassy
who's been trying to get me
for weeks.
I'm sure we'll talk again.
Enjoy your evening.
You too.
I'm gonna try a shrimp puff.
I hear good things.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Thank you. And you.
Modern dance?
You have no idea
how talented I am.
Here, you can see
who bought what sneakers when.
And the address they were
sent to.
All of these pairs have been
sold in a month?
You did good, little brother.
I asked about you all the time.
But Mother said I couldn't
see you.
Father wouldn't let me say
your name.
All I wanted to do
was be like you.
Police!
Don't worry.
Welcome.
So, the rumors are true.
This is the brother
with the magic fingers.
Selling shit through that.
Kaito, this is Hayama-san.
So tell me how it works.
My brother has a great deal
of studying to do.
I'm sure he's got a second
to fill me in.
My brother and I have set up
a website to sell sneakers.
Sneakers?
- How much you make so far?
- Hard to say.
But more than
half a million Yen.
With this box?
Holy shit.
Seriously?
Have you met the Oyabun yet,
Kaito?
He'll like you.
Brother Hayama. Kaito is a student.
He is not one of us.
Fair enough.
You have to respect
your elder brother's wishes.
But I know a goldmine
when I meet one.
Excuse me.
Are you
the famous choreographer?
Yes, I am.
And you choreographed
tonight's show?
Yes, I did. Wasn't it great?
We are touring the world.
Our next stop is Missouri.
Come with me.
Meet my family.
I know we've only
been together for a month,
and the very idea
of us being together is crazy.
But I wanna believe
that we have a future together.
What?
- Did he see me?
- Who?
That man.
I've seen him with Tozawa.
Don't worry. Nobody here
has any connection to Tozawa.
I have to go.
Hey, slow down.
Do not touch me.
Stay away from me.
How long have you been looking?
This whole time.
I definitely put it there.
Did you check everywhere?
You seem preoccupied.
Do I? Not at all.
Are you concerned
about my proposal
that we spend time together
outside of here?
I'm still thinking about it.
I just need you to be patient.
Take all the time you need.
Can you excuse me for a minute?
Sure.
What's happening?
He lost Ishii-san's bottle.
The Glenmorangie Grand Vintage.
I put it back.
I don't know where it went.
That whiskey is not cheap.
It costs fifty thousand Yen.
- I can't just order another.
- I'm sorry.
Hey, mama.
Goddamn it.
- Sam?
- Yeah?
You deal with him,
I'll deal with them, okay?
- Okay.
- Divide and conquer.
Let's find this thing.
- Who's bottle?
- Ishii-san's bottle.
Oh, right. Ishii-san's bottle.
- What's wrong with you, Kenji?
- Sorry.
I thought you might like to
share a celebratory drink, detective.
Why haven't you gone home?
I could ask the same of you.
The prosecutors liked
the arrests.
With the documents seized,
we can charge most of them
with extortion.
One of them ratted out
the Oyabun.
He and his men are going away
for a long time.
To the new ways.
You don't feel celebratory?
Nothing comes without cost.
Then let's make it worth it.
- Who is it?
- It's Chika, Tats' sister!
Wait, I'm coming.
- You promised us! You promised!
- Slow down.
- They took him!
- What?
My brother was arrested. Because
of your stupid newspaper!
Arrested?
Wait, no, that's not...
I didn't tell anyone your names.
We didn't even run the photos!
But because of your article,
the cops cracked down even harder!
What happened to
your face and hair?
I kept your names out of everything.
- I didn't tell anyone.
- There are murderers in there.
Doesn't matter what you did.
They put us all
in the same place.
I'll figure something out.
You know...
I stole a bike,
and I'm going to prison.
You helped me steal one.
So why aren't you?
You have to look out for
my sister.
She's got no one.
If the newspaper speaks up for him,
we could get him in reform school.
It doesn't matter
that he's a juvenile.
He was arrested while stealing
a motorcycle, and he hit a policeman.
Reform school is off the table.
Maruyama-san, he's been
in a holding cell for a day,
the other prisoners
have already beat him up.
It will get worse
when he is transferred.
Juvenile prisons here can be
even worse than adult ones.
Jesus.
You.
Hayama-san.
What can I do for you?
Don't be silly. You're the
genius who needs a reward.
Reward?
Come. Take a ride with me.
Tonight's gonna be special.
You'll never forget it.
Hey. It's been a while.
- How about we get a drink?
- I'm busy, Meicho-san.
Listen.
The last time
I saw you at Onyx...
I was out of line.
You tried to help me,
and I jumped to conclusions.
Please accept my apology.
I heard you got beat up.
Yeah.
I heard you got stabbed.
- You hungry?
- Starving.
Come on. I know a place.
- I've got something to ask you.
- What a surprise.
It's time you got a taste
of the town.
Let me ask you something.
In high school, you ever like a
girl but she didn't go for you?
Kind of.
What school?
Narishima Gakuen High.
Narishima Gakuen High for this
hard-working young man.
- I understand, sir.
- Same for me.
Of course.
Please!
- Which prison is he going to?
- Probably Asaka. In Saitama.
Guards there like to turn
the firehoses on prisoners.
One boy...
They stuffed
the nozzle in his ass.
And blasted the water so hard,
it ruptured his intestine.
You seem to know a lot about
juvenile detention.
Can you help this kid?
Is there someone in there you
know, who can look out for him?
Are you asking for a favor,
Meicho-san?
Yes.
I'll take care of it.
"Take care of it," like?
Make sure
he is protected inside.
And give him a place
with us when he's out.
Is there a problem with that?
No. Thank you.
And you're paying for dinner.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Maybe you should have skipped
the Kobe beef, huh?
Why are you all still here?
- Aren't you all going out for afters?
- We are. Here. With you.
- Really?
- Sit with us. Minami got some food.
Your favorite, Samantha-san.
Thank you, Kenji.
I'm sorry about earlier.
- It's no problem.
- I'm so sorry.
You didn't need to do all this.
- We did. Mama-san's working too hard.
- It's just my job.
Best job I've ever had.
This is the only club I've worked
at that felt safe. Thanks to you.
Thank you, Mama.
To Mama-san. Who should drink
more and worry less.
To Mama-san!
Kanpai!
Where are we going?
Sato-san has explained to me
what you would like me
to acquire.
And what is your response?
The architect has taken me into
his confidence.
Invited me to his home.
So I am in a position to help.
Then you will do it.
I know the value
of this information.
So if I am to do this favor,
I ask a favor in return.
And what is that?
Sole ownership of my club.
And your word that no member
of Chihara-kai
will ever enter it again.
Agreed.
But you will still pay me
twenty-five percent
of your profits
for the next six months.
I would be honored to pay the Oyabun
that for the next two months.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Alright.
- Three months.
- Agreed.
You're good at this.
You will do well in this world.
Good luck.
Please leave
a message after the...